{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4608","name":"Go! Sy Thai","address":"4240 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Cedric Lee","licenseNumber":"077787","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.06362,42.35134","geojson":{"id":"4608","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.063619025,42.3513433890001]},"properties":{"name":"Go! Sy Thai","owner":"Cedric Lee","address":"4240 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"077787","establishmentid":"4608","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622641","name":"Fresh 101 Superfood Cafe","address":"4240 Cass Ave Ste. 100","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622479","name":"Tou & Mai","address":"4240 Cass Ave, Ste. 102","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622794","name":"Spread Deli","address":"4215 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622620","name":"Cobb Corner Bar","address":"4201 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5380","name":"Alley Taco","address":"418 Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622811","name":"Avalon International Breads","address":"422 W Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5056","name":"Treat Dreams","address":"4160 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5386","name":"Detroit Royale with Cheese","address":"4163 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4646","name":"La Feria Spanish Tapas","address":"4130 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4152","name":"Slows To Go","address":"4107 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44676","inspectionDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"VENTILATION","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"Cooking equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR AND WALLS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"45173","inspectionDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) The temperature of the wash solution in spray type warewashers that use hot water to SANITIZERS may not be less than:     \r\n(1) For a stationary rack, single temperature machine, 74°C (165°F);(Pf)   \r\n(2) For a stationary rack, dual temperature machine, 66°C (150°F); (Pf)   \r\n(3) For a single tank, conveyor, dual temperature machine, 71°C (160°F);(Pf) or\r\n(4) For a multitank, conveyor, multitemperature machine, 66°C (150°F).(Pf)  \r\n(B) The temperature of the wash solution in spray-type warewashers that use chemicals to SANITIZE may not be less than 49°C (120°F). (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine wash solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 150 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41972","inspectionDate":"2018-04-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.110","violationDescription":"(A) The temperature of the wash solution in spray type warewashers that use hot water to SANITIZERS may not be less than:     \r\n(1) For a stationary rack, single temperature machine, 74°C (165°F);(Pf)   \r\n(2) For a stationary rack, dual temperature machine, 66°C (150°F); (Pf)   \r\n(3) For a single tank, conveyor, dual temperature machine, 71°C (160°F);(Pf) or\r\n(4) For a multitank, conveyor, multitemperature machine, 66°C (150°F).(Pf)  \r\n(B) The temperature of the wash solution in spray-type warewashers that use chemicals to SANITIZE may not be less than 49°C (120°F). (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine wash solution temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 150 degrees F","subProblem":"For hot water sanitizing machine","location":"DISH MACHINE","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-04-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41107","inspectionDate":"2017-12-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"40179","inspectionDate":"2017-09-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45188","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":null,"subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"40164","inspectionDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Held past time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-09-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"violationCode":"4-301.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT for cooling and heating FOOD, and holding cold and hot FOOD, shall be sufficient in number and capacity to provide FOOD temperatures as required. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Lack of Cold holding equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Install to meet requirements"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.18","violationDescription":"The wash, rinse, and SANITIZE solutions shall be maintained clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing solutions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."}]},{"inspectionid":"38179","inspectionDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"before handling ready to eat foods","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Lack of HAND WASHING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"IMPROPER Food Storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"Food","location":"FOOD SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"IMPROPER Chemical storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Lack of SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Sanitize as required above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-501.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cooked POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be cooled:\r\n         (1)  Within 2 hours, from 135ºF to 70ºF; and (P) \r\n         (2)  Within 4 hours, from 70ºF to 41ºF or less (P)\r\n(B)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared from ingredients at ambient temperature shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41F or less. (P)\r\n(C)  POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  received in compliance with LAWS   allowing a temperature above 41ºF during shipment from the supplier shall be cooled within 4 hours to 41ºF or less. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cooked food(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"From 70 degrees f to 41 degrees F for more than 4 hours","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"IMPROPER COOLING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"FRONT AREA / COOK LINE","subLocation":"IMPROPER Food Storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"4-204.115","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine shall be equipped with a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that indicates the temperature of the water:\r\n(A)  In each wash and rinse tank; (Pf) and\r\n(B)  As the water enters the hot water SANITIZING final rinse manifold or in the chemical SANITIZING solution tank. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Warewashing thermometer","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Install to meet requirements"},{"violationCode":"4-502.11","violationDescription":"(A) UTENSILS shall be maintained in a state of repair or condition that complies with the requirements specified under Parts 4-1 and 4-2 or shall be discarded.\r\n(B) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be calibrated in accordance with manufacturer's specifications as necessary to ensure their accuracy. (Pf)   \r\n(C) Ambient air temperature, water pressure, and water TEMPERATURE MEAURING DEVICES shall be maintained in good repair and be accurate within the intended range of use.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not calibrated","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-02-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Calibrate in accordance with manufacturer specifications."},{"violationCode":"4-204.117","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine that uses a chemical for SANITIZATION and that is installed after adoption of this Code by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY, shall be equipped with a device that indicates audibly or visually when more chemical SANITIZER needs to be added.(Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Chemical sanitizer level indicator","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-501.112","violationDescription":"In a mechanical operation, the temperature of the fresh hot water SANITIZING rinse as it enters the manifold may not be more than 194 F, or less than 165 F for stationary rack machines or 180 F for all other machines to assure proper sanitizing of utensils. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Dish machine final rinse temperature","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than 180 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Dishwasher","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair to provide temperature stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"DISHWASHING AREA","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"In large container","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"IMPROPER COOLING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Utilize long, shallow pans."},{"violationCode":"2-103.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall ensure that employees, practices and policies are in compliance with the code. (Pf) \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not ensuring compliance","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"In the Facility","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Person-in-charge must ensure compliance with items listed above."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Lack of Cooler thermometer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"4-501.14","violationDescription":"A WAREWASHING machine; the compartments of sinks, basins, or  other receptacles used for washing and rinsing EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, or raw FOODS, or laundering wiping cloths; and drainboards or other EQUIPMENT used to substitute for drainboards shall be cleaned as required.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing equipment","subItem":"three compartment sink basins","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean as specified above."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dried with a cloth towel","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"DISHWASHING AREA","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-05-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In water less than 135 degrees f","location":"FRONT AREA / COOK LINE","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain water at 135 degrees F or greater."},{"violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA / COOK LINE","subLocation":"Cooler(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.18","violationDescription":"The wash, rinse, and SANITIZE solutions shall be maintained clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Warewashing solutions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Near the Storage rack(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-03-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"3-302.15","violationDescription":"Raw fruits and vegetables shall be thoroughly washed to remove soil and other contaminants before being prepared or served. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Raw","subItem":"Fruits","problemDescription":"Not washed prior to prep, cooking or service","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Vegetables","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Wash prior to use."}]},{"inspectionid":"36168","inspectionDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"Lack of TIME MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide clear easy to read time marks."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"On the Food storage racks","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"COOLING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-04-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4608"}}